What else do we have?
So over here, we can also add photos.
So let's say that I wanna come over here, click new chat.
And let's say that right now, we wanna give it a photo.
So I want you to practice all the use cases.
So by clicking on this option over here, add photos and files,
I go to my computer and I bring the logo of the take of college up.
So our educational brand.
So I upload it over here.
And in this ask anything, in this input, I ask that,
okay, for example, I want chat GPT to go through the internet
and find information about this photo.
So for example, I'm not familiar with it, I just found it somewhere.
And I wanna ask that, okay, hello, chat GPT.
Look at this logo that I found.
And I don't know anything about.
So I want you to go through the internet
and give me all the information you find about it.
I'm very excited to know everything and I'm very sensitive on it,
and I'm very sensitive on it being on the information being accurate.
So Bd, right?
And for example, I can also come here and click the deep research option,
turn it on, and I send my command to see what is waiting for me, right?
Yes, so it says, thanks for sharing the logo to ensure I conduct
through the accurate research, clarify a couple of things.
Got this logo?
Are you looking for the general background on the institution
or you want details like founders, location?
Okay, no, let's say no, my friend sent it to me and I have no context.
I don't even know what it is, so introduce it to me, right?
Let's start researching, so as you see, this is the deep research that we turned on.
So it says, I'll keep you posted as soon as I have detailed and accurate information for you.
Yes, so as you see, this is the deep research, so it's going through every single information
out there, you know?
And it also provides you with the sources over here.
So anything that it says on deep research mode will come from a certain source and the
source is provided over here.
Yes, so as you see, some information is appearing, the take of college is an independent
international online platform, offering non-academic project-based tech courses.
I noticed the Udemy links didn't display content showing a template of Udemy's main
page instead of the instructor profile on one of the links were broken.
I'm gathering info on the take of college founded by Nemo Rassemi validating the total
learners and reviews to ensure the platforms missing alarms with purpose.
The outlet state, the site offers non-academic focusing on the app.
I'm noticing Nemo Rassemi as author and publisher for these books, you know, on Amazon.
So as you see, it's doing the deepest research is possible, you know?
And it's not even halfway through it yet, right?
So these options are all that you can use and what else do we have?
So this was deep research.
We also tried adding photos and files.
We also can generate to, let me say, stop.
Moving through the blog date and stamps, suggesting regular updates.
Yeah.
For some Udemy, offer these subjects.